pickysite.com 2011-09-20

# Privacy Policy / Web Design - Website Designers - Web Design Community and Web Designers Directory

**PRIVACY POLICY**

PickySite.com (hereafter referred to as PickySite) has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our website. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

**What this Privacy Statement Covers**

This privacy statement covers PickySite's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by PickySite through a website owned and operated by PickySite. 

This privacy statement does not apply to the practices of companies that PickySite does not own or control, or of persons that PickySite does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which PickySite's websites link.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

You can visit the website of PickySite without revealing any personal information. However, PickySite needs certain personal information if you wish to register for a members account, receive a PickySite newsletter, or use certain PickySite services. 

Where required, this information may include your company contact information and your personal contact information. PickySite will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to set up your members account, to provide you with requested services, and to contact you regarding new services. PickySite may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

By accessing the services of PickySite and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy statement.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

PickySite automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. PickySite may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, PickySite does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you. 

PickySite also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and PickySite assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

PickySite may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of PickySite to provide services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information.

PickySite may otherwise disclose your personal information when: 

a) We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;

b) We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;

c) We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of PickySite; 

d) We find that your actions on our website violate the PickySite Usage Guidelines for specific products or services.

**Consent**

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this statement, please do not provide any personal information to PickySite. If you have provided personal information to PickySite and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify PickySite by contacting our webmaster.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our site may link to advertisers and other sites that collect personal information about you when you leave PickySite.com and that may have privacy policies and practices that are different from ours. This type of collection or use of information is beyond PickySite.com’s control and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every site you visit before providing any information. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Be sure to visit this page frequently to find any updates we have made. Your continued use of the site after such changes have been posted indicates your consent and acceptance of such changes. 

**Effective Date**

This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on April 15, 2009.
